Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and forge ahead, drawing your own map as you go!
We can't even tell left from right
in this tempest-tossed era
Even the values we've honed
seem ready to crumble
Is the compass leading us true,
or is it leading us astray?
Nobody knows for sure!
*# Just breathe deep, close your eyes
and you'lIl find your soul guiding the way!
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and kick away the darkness!
and you're doing this for yourself too, right?
Forge ahead, painting the world in your own colors!
Edited by fedew Subtitles by HatSubs
You heard him!
Don't give up the fight!
/////
Satisfied, son of Oden?
Straw Hat'Il "best" me?
Wano's borders will open?
And everybody gets to live happily ever after?
You gotta be dreamin'!
I'm gonna...
...win, I swear it!
It will not be Luffy alone!
My people shall see to our victory!
Fool of a boy...
Momonosuke-sama! If it is our time, we shall meet our end together!
Ripe-Ripe Jutsu!
And so Momonosukeeeee..
...fell as well!
Indeed, the de facto leader of the enemy faction is dead!
If we announce it to all of Onigashima,
those filthy samurai-will lose all will to fight this time!
You're right! Let's crush their spiriiits!
Big Bro! He's alive!
Let's keep heading for the Performance Floor Stage, Nami!
Yep!
Luffy's hanging tough, so we'd better do the same!
000 Yeah!
I'm happy for Straw Hat!
Wha?!
Was that you, Klima Takt?
What in the world..
The Klima Takt...
...Spoke?!
It's so cute!
Straw Hat's gonna "best" Kaido?
Some kind of a joke, you think?
All I wanted to do was butcher him myself, that's all.
But if he's plunged into the sea, he's got to be dead by now!
You know, the more you work with him,
the more you get this odd feeling he'll somehow pull through.
C You sayin' you just here to get in the way, Trafalgar?
O It's Big Mom we're fighting.
X Grow up, Eustasser...
Let's make this a... temporary partnership.
Maybe I'm too much of a genius to have realized it myself?
But it talked! The Klima Takt I created!
No, like I've been saying, it's me! Ex-Zeus!
So how did you turn into the Klima Takt?
You were somebody's meal back there!
At that moment...
Before I knew it, my soul was leaving my body...
Go on, eat up, Hera!
I was barely hanging on as that Hera girl was about to absorb me...
Some pity Black Balls, coming your way!
Chow on these and run!
Zeus!
But then you reached out to me with the Klima Takt..
Eat them, Zeus!
Pull yourself together!
Thanks for being my meal, Zeus-senpai!
And it seems like at the instant Hera bit down, I was pushed into this baton!
Check me out now!
I'm born again!
What? Ugh, can I maybe not have an annoying talking weapon?
Oh, yeah! You still haven't let me off the hook!
Just get out already!
But I can't get out, not without Mama's power...
Oh, hey! There's the stage!
Tama, get there and give them orders!
Kay!
To all those here at Onigashima, may I have your attention, pleeeease!
The enemy general, Momo-
Bao Huang-sama, behind you!
It's the Straw Hats!
Ah, Usohachi-kun!
Ulti-Mortar!
Wh-
Usopp!
XX
It ever so is all this runt's fault, is it not?!
O-Tama!
All 'cause of her, it's been nothing but betrayal after betrayal by our underlings!
And to top it all, she even had Big Mom under her thumb!
She's still standing even after taking that attack head-on?!
Pay-Pay got all beat up Obecause of you!
What part of "Stop" did you not understand?!
Uh?!
You can do that?!
Nami, just use the Takt like you always do! I'm gonna help!
Her skin's just way too hard!
But Mama's attack really messed her up inside!
We can knock her out with a Lightning Blast!
We can't! That's overkill!
O-Tama would get caught in it!
C'mon, Black Kabuto..
I really need you right now..
You're all dead meat!
Sure-Kill Green Star:
Sargasso!
There, they're split up! Now, Nami!
Okay!
Even after they lost Straw Hat Luffy,
none of them surrendered.
-AIGIS
...a total of 5,000 troops incapacitated.
The Animal Kingdom Pirates had 24,000 fit for combat, and the rebels 3,000.
However, all of the Pleasures and Waiters on the Performance Floor...
...turned against Queen-sama,
20 07 (20,000) (7000)
The diminishing gap in army strength is most unexpected...
The situation is wholly unpredictable.
And we are in possession of intelligence that may further alter conditions...
H-Here they come! It's the Gifters!
This is really bad!
BriS
B Gifters Elite Corps, reporting in!
Is it true that the Pleasures and Waiters on this floor...
...revolted against Queen-sama?!
Yeah, sure is!
Who do they think they even are? They're just some expendable trash!
Let's just throw 'em in the incinerator with the rest of the garbage!
Get rid of all the backstabbers on this floor!
BriS
Gorilla Punch: Starring My Fist!
Weather Egg!
Come forth, thundercloud!
Kaaay!
Zeus?!
Not exactly, not anymore!
C'mon Nami, gimme a new name already!
Err...
ErT...
What? What is it?
I wanna know!
Fluff!
I am the mighty Zeus!
Nami's right-hand man! Prepare yourself!
Let's do this, Zeus!
You damn dirty..
Ulti!
This little game of cat-and-mouse with you...
...is gonna be over after this!
Lightning Blast!
3 3
/11 ||
||
HI
1/ You're kidding!
Yeah, it's over, all right...
No, it's not over!
It's not over 'til I've done my job...
...and hit my target!
Eh?
Ulti-sama has been eliminateeeed!
She follows Page One-sama..
...and now two members of the Flying Six have been done iiiin!
Whaaaa?!
No freaking way!
That's never happened before!
Don't tell me we're losing!
Bao Huang-sama, all of Onigashima heard you!
Oh, no!
I announced it by accident!
That was a total lie! I take it baaack!
So that one's like a transmitter, then!
In that case..!
Huh?
Sure-Kill Green Star:
Devil!
Huuuh?! What's this?!
What the heck is this monsterrrr?!
Hey, Tama!
I don't know how it all works, but that one's a transmitter!
Your commands'll reach the whole island!
Speak!
Kay!
looo
I'm O-Tama!
Was that a kid?!
O-Tama-chan?!
Why's she here on Onigashima?!
There she is! Master!
Drink up!
Sing!
Gorgeous, is it not, O-Toko?
Mm-hmm!
The Fire Festival is held in memory of the deceased..
And so we build a fire, such that it reaches the heavens.
I wonder if Daddy's watching?
Aye, indeed...
The skies are quite clear...
I am sure he is watching over you, and the fate of our land...
Uh-huh!
Someone's there!
Whuh?!
There is somebody there!
Hey, isn't that Straw Hat?!
How can you hear a voice under the sea?!
Who cares, give him a hand already!
On the double! Is he alive?!
What's a freakin' brat...
...doing on the battlefield?!
What happened, Bao Huang?!
Who're you?!
O-Tama!
Tama, pull yourself together!
Not even the tiniest gripe out of you, huh, Jinbe?
At first, it was 5,000 111 against 30,000!
Naturally, you outnumber us.
It would be foolish to assume I'd be fighting you one-on-one.
You've got a good grasp of the situation!
Royal pain in my ass!
It's our job not to let you top officers go unchecked!
They just keep comin'...
There's no end to these underlings!
You can be prepared to die all you want...
But in the end, it's a game of numbers.
That's what makes this total war!
Don't blame me...
O O
That brat! She's still messin' around up there?!
Hey! I want her yanked down from there yesterday!
Let's go!
Yeah!
You can do it, O-Tama!
Go for it!
0 T-To all my friends that ate my Kibi Dango!
I'm asking y'all a favor!
Please join Big Bro Luffy's...
...and Momonosuke-kun's group!
Let's all take out Kaido, together!
Ain't no way us Animal Kingdom Pirates...
.'re gonna follow orders from some runt!
Certainly, at once, Master!
It would be our pleasure!
Down with Kaido!
EEN Why, ya little!
You all lost it or somethin'?!
Briscola-san, what's the matter?
Let's deal with those dirty traitors already!
Easy as pie, Master!
Gorilla Punch: Starring My Fist!
For our Master!
Right, you heard her orders!
Daifugo! Gazelle-man!
Let's get in there!
Aye!
Leave it to me, Master!
There's something weird about the Gifters!
What are they doing?!
Down with Kaido! Let's go!
Follow me, folks!
Our strength combined..
...is yours to command, Master! O
Thanks, everybody!
What the hell is this?!
Like I said, he's a goner.
And like I said, no curses!
Without the Captain here, how do we even handle this?!
Aaarrrgh!
For now, let's clear his lungs!
One, two!
11.
1  Step aside!
Think you might've been a little too.. forceful?
He'll be fine.
5 'Cause he's rubber.
Not okay!
Yeah, he's totally a goner...
Captain, save uuuus!
V So h-hi.. So h-hii...
So hiiigh!
Entrust everything to my Ninja Arts!
Ninja Art: Great Kite!
Our first task: landing somewhere safe!
That was frightening.!
I suppose this means I managed to escape, aye?
But...
...what is going on?!
My subjects... Are they still all right?
Kiku! Kin'emon!
My subjeeeects!
Kaido!
That's "Father" to you..
...Yamato!
No, I have come to sever those chains!
You've come to "sever the chains" between father and son, eh?
Don't make me laugh!
What's left for you?
Straw Hat's disappeared beneath the waves...
And so has the son of Kozuki Oden...
If you have the will to fight, you should've been there to protect what needs protecting!
Neither Luffy nor Momonosuke-kun are in need of my protection!
They are...
...allies, alongside whom I fight!
You little snot-nosed brat..
You're really planning to break off your shackles and leave?!
Aye! I will set out to sea with Luffy!
After I have kicked you out of this country,
Kaido!
Not just any place'll do, Yamato!
I'm stayin' right here because this is Wano!
There's no way you can beat me!
You will be the Shogun of Wano, Yamato!
I refuse!
I know that I cannot defeat you..
However..!
Luffy is the man Kozuki Oden was waiting for!
Until his return,
I shall be holding you here!
Don't expect me to go easy on you...
...Yamato!
CUNHINUED